Kheel Center Current Documents Correspondence /4212
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Federation of Salaried Unions, 1950-1955 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  November 16 1950 - March 9 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. Federation of Westinghouse Salaried Unions, 1955-1958 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  April 8 1955 - November 28 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Seafarers' International Union of North America AFL, 1945-1961 (Box 6, Folder 127)
  November 17 1945 - June 9 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Seafarers International Union. Sailors' Union of the Pacific, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  October 1 1959
- Union Correspondence. Western Service Station Employees Union, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 129)
  December 29 1958 - October 31 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Sheet Metal Workers' International Association AFL, 1948-1961 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  January 12 1948 - June 16 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Brotherhood of Shoe and Allied Craftsmen, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 131)
  March 26 1951 - February 14 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Shoe Workers of America CIO, 1946-1952 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  November 12 1946 - August 22 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Boot and Shoe Workers Union AFL, 1946-1955 (Box 6, Folder 133)
  November 12 1946 - August 5 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. Lewiston-Auburn Shoe Workers Protective Association, 1952-1954 (Box 6, Folder 134)
  January 11 1952 - August 5 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. Society of Skilled Trades of Genesee County, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  February 18 1957
- Union Correspondence. Order of Sleeping Car Conductors, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  January 19 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters AFL, 1945-1958 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  December 11 1945 - March 28 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. South Carolina State Federation of Labor, 1950-1974 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  February 2 1950 - March 19 1974
- Labor Union Correspondence. South Carolina State Industrial Union Council, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  April 16 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. South Dakota State Federation of Labor, 1949-1953 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  September 27 1949 - July 20 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the US and Canada, 1945- 1959 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  December 20 1945 - September 30 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees AFL, 1945-1961 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  December 12 1945 - October 23 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Steel Workers Federation, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  May 24 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Stereotypers' s and Electrotypers' Union of North America AFL, 1949-1959 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  September 12 1949 - February 11 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Stone and Allied Products Workers of America CIO, 1950-1959 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  December 6 1950 - October 8 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. Journeymen Stonecutters' Association of North America AFL, 1946-1954 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  July 25 1946 - October 27 1954
- Stove Mounters International Union of North America, 1950-1961 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  September 21 1950 - September 18 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Amalgamated Association of Street Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America AFL, 1948-1961 (Box 6, Folder 148)
  May 7 1948 - May 19 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Council of Sugar Workers and Allied Industries Unions, 1949-1955 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  June 23 1949 - April 8 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. Independent Union of Milwaukee Taxicab Drivers and Employees, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  November 17 1950
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Federation of Teachers AFL, 1945-1961 (Box 6, Folder 151)
  December 11 1945 - September 18 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Council of Western Electric Technical Employees, 1950-1953 (Box 6, Folder 152)
  February 14 1950 - March 16 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. Conference of Technical Personnel Bell Telephone Co., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 153)
  July 18 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. Commercial Telegraphers Union AFL, 1945-1960 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  November 12 1945 - January 11 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Telephone Organizations, 1948-1959 (Box 6, Folder 155)
  August 12 1948 - August 18 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. Empire State Telephone Union, 1950-1952 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  March 2 1950 - October 23 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Connecticut Union of Telephone Workers, Inc., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 157)
  November 25 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. Tennessee, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 158)
  June 19 1953 - August 23 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. Tennessee State Labor Council AFL-CIO, 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 159)
  July 24 1956 - January 6 1958
- Union Correspondence. Texas, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 160)
  April 15 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. Texas State AFL-CIO, 1959-1961 (Box 6, Folder 161)
  September 13 1959 - February 6 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Texas State Federation of Labor, 1949-1955 (Box 6, Folder 162)
  September 27 1949 - February 12 955
- Labor Union Correspondence. Texas State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1957 (Box 6, Folder 163)
  February 16 1950 - January 15 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. Federated Independent Texas Unions, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 164)
  January 12 1950
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Textile Workers of America AFL, 1947-1960 (Box 6, Folder 165)
  July 31 1947 - November 4 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Textile Workers Union of America CIO, 1946-1960 (Box 6, Folder 166)
  September 12 1946 - January 21 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Tobacco Workers International Union AFL, 1947-1958 (Box 6, Folder 167)
  March 26 1947 - April 14 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. The Society of Tool and Die Craftsmen of America, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 168)
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Association of Tool Craftsmen, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 169)
  January 2 1957 - February 2 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. Colored Trainmen of America, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 170)
- Labor Union Correspondence. Transport Workers Union of America CIO, 1946-1953 (Box 6, Folder 171)
  July 25 1946 - November 24 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Transportation Association, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 172)
  January 28 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Transport Service Employees of America CIO, 1950-1954 (Box 6, Folder 173)
  January 12 1950 - November 30 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Typographical Union AFL, 1947-1959 (Box 6, Folder 174)
  October 24 1947 - June 2 1959
- Labor Union Correspondence. Federation of University Employees, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  August and September 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. Upholsterers' International Union of North America AFL, 1946-1961 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  November 8 1946 - July 7 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Utah State Federation of Labor, 1949-1953 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  September 27 1949 - September 22 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. Utah State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  February 16 1950 - March 31 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Fishermen and Allied Workers' Union, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  August 19 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. Utility Workers of America CIO, 1945-1961 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  December 12 1945 - October 19 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Brotherhood of Utility Workers of New England, Inc., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  January 13 1950
- Labor Union Correspondence. Vermont Federation of Labor, 1949-1966 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  September 27 1949 - January 25 1966
- Labor Union Correspondence. Vermont State Industrial Union Council, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Labor Union Correspondence. Virginia, 1958-1960 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  October 21 1958 - September 16 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Wisconsin State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1956 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  February 16 1950 - January 16 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. The Women's Educational and Industrial Union, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  January 2 and 7 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Wood Carvers Association of North America, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Woodworkers of America, 1952-1961 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  November 7 1952 - March 30 1961
- Labor Union Correspondence. Workers Defense League, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  October 1 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Workmen's Circle, 1953-1958 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  October 22 1953 - October 31 1958
- Labor Union Correspondence. West Writers Guild of America, Inc., 1955-1960 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  March 2 1955 - December 6 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Wyoming State Federation of Labor, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  February 3 1950
- Labor Union Correspondence. Wyoming State Industrial Union Council, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Labor Union Correspondence. Alabama State Federation of Labor, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  January 18 1950
- Labor Union Correspondence. Alabama State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1954 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  February 23 1950 - November 6 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. Alaska Federation of Labor, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  February 2 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Federation of Labor, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Federation of Labor 1952 - 1953 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  February 25 1952 - March 20 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Federation of Labor Building and Construction Trades Department, 1951-1956 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  December 17 1951 - July 24 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Federation of Labor Metal Trades Department, 1946-1955 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  August 13 1946 - May 16 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. National Legislative Council AFL, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  April 11 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. Railway Employes' Department AFL, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  June 19 1951 - November 14 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Union Label Trades Department AFL, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  November 13 and 21 1947
- Labor Union Correspondence. Workers Education Bureau AFL, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  May, June and July 1950
- Labor Union Correspondence. American Federation of Labor, 1946-1949 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  June 26 1946 - July 7 1949
- Labor Union Correspondence. Arizona State Federation of Labor, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Labor Union Correspondence. Arkansas State Federation of Labor, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Labor Union Correspondence. Arkansas State Industrial Union Council, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Union United Automobile Workers of America AFL, 1945-1956 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  December 11 1945 - January 18 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Colorado State Federation of Labor, 1948-1950 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  June 10 1948 - January 18 1950
- Labor Union Correspondence. Colorado State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1956 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  February 16 1950 - October 1 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1946-1952 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  May 7 1946 - March 17 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1953-1955 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  November 19 1953 - October 17 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. Committee to Abolish Discrimination CIO, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  July 26 and August 1 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. Community Services Committee, 1951-1954 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  October 30 1951 - June 15 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. Latin American Committee CIO, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  September 24 1952 - November 19 1952
- Labor Union Correspondence. Maritime Committee CIO, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  June 26 and August 3 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. Telephone Workers Organizing Committee CIO, 1948-1951 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  February 5 1948 - June 6 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. Political Action Committee CIO, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  March 3 and 18 1949
- Labor Union Correspondence. Connecticut State Federation of Labor, 1949-1956 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  June 6 1949 - August 28 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Connecticut State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1954 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  February 16 1950 - August 16 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. Cook County Industrial Union Council, 1955-1960 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  March 21 1955 - February 5 1960
- Labor Union Correspondence. Delaware State Federation of Labor, 1950-1956 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  January 18 1950 - February 16 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Delaware State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1953 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  February 16 1950 - February 9 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America CIO, 1946-1954 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  December 13 1946 - October 18 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. Georgia State Federation of Labor, 1950-1954 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  January 18 1950 - August 16 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. Georgia State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1957 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  February 16 1950 - April 4 1957
- Labor Union Correspondence. Government and Civic Workers Organization Committee, 1951-1954 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  November 19 1951 - October 19 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Handbag, Luggage, Belt and Novelty Workers' Union AFL, 1945-1955 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  December 28 1945 - March 30 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Office and Professional Workers of America CIO, 1945-1951 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  December 3 1945 - July 26 1951
- Labor Union Correspondence. Oil Workers International Union CIO, 1945-1954 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  December 21 1945 - November 23 1954
- Labor Union Correspondence. International Brotherhood of Paper Makers AFL, 1946-1955 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  February 15 1946 - November 17 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Paperworkers of America CIO, 1945-1955 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  December 20 1945 - November 21 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. United Public Workers of America CIO, 1946-1953 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  December 4 1946 - January 15 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. Telephone Unions. Miscellaneous, 1946-1955 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  January 16 1946 - May 19 1955
- Labor Union Correspondence. Tennessee State Federation of Labor, 1950-1956 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  February 2 1950 - March 14 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Tennessee State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1953 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  February 16 1950 - July 20 1953
- Labor Union Correspondence. Virginia State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1956 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  February 16 1950 - February 8 1956
- Labor Union Correspondence. Virginia State Federation of Labor, 1943-1954 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  January 23 1943 - May 21 1954